Clark Nelson

Full Stack Developer from Chicago, Illinois

SUMMARY

I am an intermediate web developer with five years experience developing and designing responsive websites using modern JavaScript frameworks.

I'm fascinated by the evolution of the world wide web and the technologies that we use to access it. I believe in simple interfaces that provide powerful functionality.

EDUCATION

B.S. Computer Science

DePaul University 2016

EXPERIENCE

Freelance Front-end Development

December 2014 - December 2016

Worked solo then in a small team to create sites for clients while finishing college.

Student at Designation.io

July 2014 - August 2014

Had an opportunity to learn more about JavaScript, UX, UI, and Node at this summer bootcamp

Intern at Neoteric Design

June 2014 - July 2014

Mentors who taught me design while I created a Ruby on Rails project management application

SKILLS

Development

JavaScript Applications using React.js, Meteor.js, and Node.js

Semantic web markup using SCSS and BEM

Mobile Application Development with Swift or Java

Basic Systems Development with Java and C/C++

Basic Linux Web Server Administration

Design

Layout Design using Sketch

User Experience

Typography / Color

Others

Agile Development Methodology

Great taste in music

Website: https://clarknelson.com
LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/clarknelson
GitHub: https://github.com/jailbot
Email: mail@clarknelson.com
Phone: 630-310-6686